Hello.
こんにちは
It's been a while.
久 しぶりだね
Yes, it's been a while.
はい、久しぶりです
I got scared.
怖くなったね
Now, usually,
今、普段、
A fun school?
楽 しい学校?
fun.
楽しい
Are you playing with friends?
友達と遊んでるの?
Yeah.
うん
Are you in contact?
接触してる?
yes.
はい
What are you doing?
どんなことしてるの?
Recently...
最近は...
Have you been to the mountains?
山のこに行ったの?
yes.
はい
With friends?
友達と?
Yes, with friends.
はい、友達と
Mountain?
山?
Do you like Yamakawa?
山川好きなの?
Yes, I like mountains.
はい、山好きです
You mean on a trip?
旅行でってこと?
A day trip.
日帰りで
A day trip?
日 帰りで?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Did you go all the way to the top?
上まで行ったの?
I went.
行きました
Was the view nice?
景色良かった?
Yeah.
うん
That's rare.
珍しいね
Is there Yamakawa?
山川あるか
You like it.
好きなんだね
What's here?
ここには何?
The crab went to Disney.
カニはディズニーに行きました
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほどね
That's interesting.
面白いね
That kind of thing...
そういうのはね、ちょっと...
Looks like a student.
学 生っぽい
Did you have sex?
エッチしました?
I haven't.
してないです
It's sudden though.
突然ですけど
It’s him, right?
彼でしょ?
I'm not there.
いないです
yes.
そう
Just a little while ago.
ちょっとね、前ね
first time.
初めて
how was it?
どうだった?
Before.
前は
What is your first impression?
一番の感想は?
It hurt at first, but it felt good at the end.
最初は痛かったけど、最後は気持ち良かった
See you again, I didn't think I'd see you again.
またね、会えると思わなかったよ
Hey, you're so cute.
ねえ、あんま可愛い
But once you get used to the camera...
でもカメラ慣れたら...
I don't know.
分かんない
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
There's no child who doesn't understand.
分かんない子ないでしょ
Let me sleep on my own.
自分でさ、寝かせてさ
show me.
見せて
Down below.
下に
That's a little honest.
少し素直だね
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
So cute.
すごく可愛い
You're wearing pants.
パンツ履いてるね
It smells like a student.
学生の匂いがする
deep.
深い
Your body is delicious.
体は美味しいね
Difficult to take off.
脱 ぎづらい
You wear it all the time, right?
いつも着てるんでしょ
That's who I am, always.
そういう自分だね、いつも
It's cute.
可愛いね
I took it off.
脱ぎやがった
picture?
え?
What should I do?
どうしたらいいの?
cute.
可愛い
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
It's not coming out at all.
全然出てないじゃん
Your legs are beautiful.
綺麗だね、足ね
You're doing great.
立派してるね
Haven't you grown up?
成長したんじゃない?
I'm doing it after all, really.
やっぱりしてるね、本当
Is it like this at school?
学校でもこうなの?
Are you going to school?
学校するの?
do not.
しない
Play by yourself?
自分で遊ぶ?
I haven't done it.
やってない
It tickled me.
くすぐったね
く すぐったね
It came out.
出てきたね
Even your waist is completely visible.
腰になるのも丸見えだよ
You're moving your hips by yourself.
自分で腰動いてるね
It's so erotic, pull the strings.
すごいエロいよ、糸引いて
Underwear too, like this.
下着もね、こんな
I'll take this home too.
これも持って帰るね
The style is really nice.
スタイルはめちゃくちゃいいね
That's really cool, style.
めちゃめちゃいいじゃん、スタイル
It's okay, look.
いいじゃん、ほら
It's based.
ベースちゃう
Spilled legs, shoulders and legs.
足、肩足こぼれ
This has become a regular occurrence for me.
これ、私、恒例されちゃうんだけど
It's really squishy.
すごいムシュムシュだよね
spread your legs
足開いて
hey.
ね
With my own two hands.
自 分の両手でさ
Pussy spread open
おまんこ開いと
child.
こ
oh yeah.
そうそう
It looks like a mess.
め ちゃくちゃ見えるよ
You like necks, right?
首好きでしょ
Your hips are moving.
腰動いてるね
I'm moving my hips on my own
自分で腰動いてるで
Sho.
しょ
It's amazing and delicious.
すごい 美味しいよ
copper?
どう?
You'll be on your knees.
膝立ちになってくるんですね
It's so delicious.
すごい美味しい